<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_Fleetkind</defName>
		<label>fleetkind</label>
		<description>Fleetkind were a misguided attempt at creating a human xenotype capable of flourishing on their own, completely isolated from other external societies. A properly established fleetkind outpost can generate its own electricity and easily replenish its numbers.\n\nFleetkind deviate greatly from baseline humans, and they are often seen as too strange to interact with.</description>
		<descriptionShort>A misguided attempt at creating a human xenotype capable of flourishing on their own. They deviate greatly from baseline humans, and they are often seen as too strange to interact with.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_Fleetkind</iconPath>
		<combatPowerFactor>0.8</combatPowerFactor>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li>Hair_BaldOnly</li>
			<li>Beard_NoBeardOnly</li>
			<li>AG_AerofleetHead</li>
			<li>AG_GasBags</li>
			<li>AG_AsexualFission</li>
			<li>AG_SlimeBody</li>
			<li>AG_UnsettlingAppearance</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Social</li>
			<li>Delicate</li>
			<li>AptitudeStrong_Animals</li>
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_Helixien</defName>
		<label>helixan</label>
		<description>The lowest of the low on the Rim, helixans were created as a human xenotype that would revel in the presence of decay, filth and refuse. Capable of exuding a foul-smelling, corrosive gas that produces an uncomfortable, itchy sensation in living beings. This gas is mostly harmless, unless it comes into contact with decaying organic matter: it greatly accelerates corpse rotting, liberating a black putrid liquid known as "purge fluid" or corpse bile. The helixans feed through the skin by contacting the liquid sludge, although they can also feed on other organic matter if needed.</description>
		<descriptionShort>Revolting slug-like humans that feed on corpses and decay.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_Helixien</iconPath>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li>Hair_BaldOnly</li>
			<li>Beard_NoBeardOnly</li>
			<li>AG_SlugBody</li>
			<li>AG_SlugFace</li>
			<li>AG_CorpseFeeding</li>
			<li>AG_LungRotStrength</li>
			<li>AG_Beauty_VeryVeryUgly</li>
			<li>AG_ColdSlowness</li>
			<li>AG_ChameleonVision</li>
			<li>Immunity_Strong</li>
			<li>MoveSpeed_Slow</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Cooking</li>
			<li>AG_SlugVoice</li>
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_Animusen</defName>
		<label>animusen</label>
		<description>Animusen were genetically spliced with Animus Vox genes to create a cold-thriving human xenotype with a much better -and less aggressive- disposition than Yttakin.\n\nAnimusen have strong psychic abilities, and they are very attuned to the feelings of others, often being valued as adept counsellors.</description>
		<descriptionShort>A cold-thriving human xenotype with a much better -and less aggressive- disposition than Yttakin, and powerful psychic abilities.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_Animusen</iconPath>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li>Beard_NoBeardOnly</li>
			<li>AG_AnimusEars</li>
			<li>AG_FoxFace</li>
			<li>AG_FoxTail</li>
			<li>AG_ColdSpeed</li>
			<li>MeleeDamage_Weak</li>
			<li>Libido_High</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Plants</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Mining</li>
			<li>AG_UVSensitivity_Minor</li>
			<li>AG_PsychicAbility_Masterful</li>
			<li>MaxTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_Lapis</defName>
		<label>lapis</label>
		<description>Where dirtmoles are unable to thrive due to inhospitable conditions, the lapis excel. Created by ultra-greedy corporations eager to wring the very last resources out of desolate, mineral rich planets, the lapis are a xenotype adapted to living basically without organic food, but at a hefty cost: they must continually search for minerals to feed themselves and sustain their strange metabolism. Lapis are practical and brusque, preferring to keep to themselves in most cases.</description>
		<descriptionShort>A xenotype of rocky looking humans adapted to living basically without organic food, but at a hefty cost: they must continually search for minerals to feed themselves and sustain their strange metabolism.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_Lapis</iconPath>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li>AG_Foodless</li>
			<li>WoundHealing_Slow</li>
			<li>AG_RockSpurs</li>
			<li>AG_RockyBody</li>
			<li>AG_MetalEater</li>
			<li>AG_ReactiveArmour</li>
			<li>AG_MineralShock</li>
			<li>AG_MineralOverdrive</li>
			<li>AptitudeRemarkable_Mining</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Artistic</li>
			<li>MinTemp_SmallIncrease</li>
			<li>AG_MiningYield_High</li>
			<li>Beard_NoBeardOnly</li>
			<li>Hair_BaldOnly</li>
			<li>MaxTemp_LargeIncrease</li>
			<li>AG_SpeedByTemperature</li>
			<li>PsychicAbility_Dull</li>
			<li>Beauty_Ugly</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Plants</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Animals</li>
			<li>AG_SlowGestation</li>
			<li>AG_RockVoice</li>
			<li>AG_PebbleBlood</li>
			
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_Wretch</defName>
		<label>wretch</label>
		<description>A testament to the horrible dangers of genetic engineering, wretches are malformed and miserable creatures produced by genetic testing gone awry. The genome of wretches is so twisted and unstable that constant, wild mutations occur every day, being erased and replaced the following morning. These mutations can be hugely beneficial, or they can condemn the wretch to a short life of misery and pain.</description>
		<descriptionShort>Malformed and miserable creatures produced by genetic testing gone awry. Subject to daily unstable mutations that can rewrite their genome completely.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_Wretch</iconPath>
		<inheritable>false</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li>AG_HeavilyScarred</li>
			<li>AG_SingleEar</li>
			<li>AG_SingleWing</li>
			<li>AG_UnstableMutationCatastrophic</li>
			<li>Sterile</li>
			<li>Skin_LightGray</li>
			<li>Skin_SlateGray</li>
			<li>Skin_InkBlack</li>
			
			
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_Taukai</defName>
		<label>taukai</label>
		<description>Named after the ancient Lithuanian word for "grease", the taukai are a very strange human xenotype, created to withstand extremely radioactive environments. The flesh of the taukai is slimy, looking like molten wax, and full of physical abnormalities, deformities and tumors. Their tissues are constantly regenerating and morphing, causing the formation of dangerous carcinomas. They have however an extraordinary ability to order their bodies to repurpose these carcinomas and use them for several beneficial designs.</description>
		<descriptionShort>A xenotype of constantly morphing, cancerous afflicted people. They constantly get carcinomas and can repurpose them to get powerful buffs.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_Taukai</iconPath>
		<inheritable>false</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li>AG_CancerousBody</li>
			<li>AG_CancerousFace</li>
			<li>AG_Teratogenesis</li>
			<li>AG_HealingTouch</li>
			<li>AG_TeratogenicManipulation</li>
			<li>AG_TeratogenicSwiftness</li>
			<li>AG_TeratogenicStamina</li>
			<li>AG_TeratogenicBurst</li>
			<li>AG_SurvivalInstinct_Low</li>
			<li>AG_RegenerationMinor</li>
			<li>AG_Filthy</li>
			<li>AG_FrailSkin</li>
			<li>ToxicEnvironmentResistance_Total</li>
			<li>AG_Painless</li>
			<li>AG_Beauty_VeryVeryUgly</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Artistic</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Social</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Medicine</li>
			
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_Hiveling</defName>
		<label>hiveling</label>
		<description>The result of an escaped experiment of the Sophian Empire, hivelings are barely human, thoroughly infused as they are with insectoid organs and genetic advantages. Hivelings thrive in heavily polluted environments, being strengthened by them. They are completely sterile, reproducing by implanting their parasitic eggs in still-living prisoners, and evolving their hive by acquiring new genes from them.\n\nHivelings are usually reviled by other human xenotypes.</description>
		<descriptionShort>Barely human, insectoid-like mutants that reproduce via parasitic infestation.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_Hiveling</iconPath>
		<inheritable>false</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li>AG_ParasiticStinger</li>
			<li>AG_Spinnerets</li>
			<li>AG_InsectRally</li>
			<li>AG_InsectBlood</li>
			<li>AG_InsectJellyProduction</li>
			<li>PsychicAbility_Dull</li>
			<li>ToxicEnvironmentResistance_Total</li>
			<li>FireWeakness</li>
			<li>MeleeDamage_Strong</li>
			<li>Sterile</li>
			<li>AG_MothWings</li>
			<li>AG_UnsettlingAppearance</li>
			<li>AG_BeetleMandibles</li>
			<li>AG_FormicAntennas</li>
			<li>Skin_PaleYellow</li>
			<li>PollutionRush</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Artistic</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Social</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Crafting</li>
			
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_MindDevourer</defName>
		<label>mind devourer</label>
		<description>A xenotype inspired by the old eldritch folklore tales from old Earth, the Chthonian visage of mind devourers inspires terror and intense uneasiness. They are masters of the psychic arts, being capable of projecting their mental powers and using their mind as a fearsome weapon, as well as devouring the brains of their victims and extracting valuable knowledge from them.\n\nHivelings are usually reviled by other human xenotypes.</description>
		<descriptionShort>A xenotype of powerful brain devouring psychics that are reviled by any other humans around the Rim.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_MindDevourer</iconPath>
		<inheritable>false</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li>AG_EldritchVisage</li>
			<li>AG_Skin_DeepPurple</li>
			<li>AG_OrnateEldritchHorns</li>
			<li>AG_FaceTentacles</li>
			<li>AG_InsanityBlast</li>
			<li>AG_UnstableMind</li>
			<li>AG_DevourBrains</li>
			<li>AG_TarBlood</li>
			<li>AG_FrailBack</li>
			<li>AG_UnderdevelopedTeeth</li>
			<li>AG_FrailSkin</li>
			<li>PsychicAbility_Extreme</li>
			<li>MeleeDamage_Weak</li>
			<li>AG_BrittleBones</li>
			<li>AG_GutturalVoice</li>
			<li>AG_GauntBody</li>
			
			
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>AG_RandomCustom</defName>
		<label>random custom</label>
		<description>This will transform the xenotype of the pawn into one of the custom xenotypes created by the player at random.</description>
		<descriptionShort>This will transform the xenotype of the pawn into one of the custom xenotypes created by the player at random.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/AG_RandomCustom</iconPath>
		
		<genes>
			<li>AlphaGenes_Randomizer</li>
			
			
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
</Defs>